Can I help you
with that?
Thanks.
Morgan Bote gave
me your number.
Are you good at this?
Yeah.
I know what I'm doing.
A Russian named Pavlovich
ordered Morgan Bote's murder
to protect a business deal
of his in Afghanistan.
He also ordered mercenaries
to Afghanistan
to protect that deal.
Dad?
Can you take me off speaker?
Shit. Shit. Shit.
No. wait! Wait!
The men that killed
Emily were his men.
Morgan Bote wasn't
his only target.
Who was his other target?
The Dixons.
-Marcia and Henry.
-Why?
Hamzad's lawyer. she
wanted to tell you something.
something she was afraid to say
over the phone.
Maybe she knows.
Then we're going to London.
Because fuck him.
I wanna hurt him. Don't you?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hey.
It's you.
Hey. You're--
I am.
We-We met...
When I had crutches
for my thing.
you helped me onto the bus.
I did.
I was wondering if I was ever
gonna run into you again.
Is this your way home from work?
No. no. no. it's not.
Gotcha.
I--
It was. but I quit my job.
Oh. congratulations.
Did I just say
"congratulations"?
It's okay.
Let me try that again.
So you quit your job.
What a wide variety of
experiences that might involve.
How are you feeling about this?
Seems like someone else
might want to quit their job.
Can you tell?
What do you do?
And you wanna make a difference.
so you pour all of yourself into
it. and you make the sacrifices.
But eventually it gets
hard to tell
where the work ends
and you begin.
It's hard to feel good
about participating in
your own erasure in that way.
But it's hard
leaving something
that may cost pieces of you
in the leaving.
I lost my best friend recently.
Just before the end. he started
to have the same questions.
"Is this the only way to live?
Is this all we are?"
I couldn't hear him back then.
And now...
...it's the only thing
I can think about.
We don't live in a place
that makes it easy
to ask those kinda questions.
Yeah.
But. hey. you got out.
Maybe that's the first step
towards something.
So...
congratulations?
What do you want?
Wasn't easy to find you.
I think Morgan Bote
sent you an email
just before he was murdered.
I need you to show me
what it said.
Mr. and Mrs. Dixon.
Welcome.
I have you checked into
room 1409.
You have anything
on the 12th floor?
Let me check.
Actually. we do.
I can put you in 1231.
Hmm. Lower.
I beg your pardon. sir?
Anything. uh.
between 01 and 05. please.
Odd
not even.
Thanks very much.
Thank you. sir.
Dad?
Can you take me off speaker?
Shit. Shit.
No. wait! Wait!
I miss you. Daddy.
This feeling just doesn't wanna
be turned off.
Maybe it's okay to be angry.
There is a time
when anger can help.
This isn't it.
We need answers
we don't even understand
the questions for yet.
We need our wits.
Pavlovich--
he dies before this is
all said and done.
That much is certain.
When it's time for the anger
to play its role in that.
it won't be hard to find.
Scorched-earth.
Yeah.
Okay.
We've got 24 hours
before this meeting is
supposed to go down.
You wanna catch a show?
That was a joke.
That was funny.
Maybe we should talk about
the meeting. how to manage it.
Morgan talked to me
about it a little.
Yeah? What did he say?
He said that Pavlovich
is connected somehow
to this deal for
Hamzad's mineral deposit.
-We don't know how.
-Mmm.
Nina Kruger. Hamzad's lawyer.
knows something about it.
and we have to figure out
what she knows.
That's what you have to get
from her.
What we should talk about
is how you plan to do that.
He said there were
three kinds of lawyers.
The kind that would do
anything for a client.
and the kind that would
do anything to be a client.
and that I should figure out
which one she is quickly.
What was the third?
He said that only
an idiot would accept
that there's only two kinds
of anything in this world.
even if we can't imagine
the third yet.
Yeah. yeah. Right.
What else did he say?
He said
all tradecraft is waged
wielding two weapons in concert.
Hmm.
See. in your left hand.
you have your empathy.
Uh-huh.
I told him that sounded
awful familiar.
Hey. he may have been
an asshole.
but that asshole understood
the game
better than anyone I ever knew.
He taught me well.
It's a scary idea.
This weapon
that I've been given.
In order to wield it.
you have to be okay never
trusting anybody ever again.
Never getting close
to anybody ever again.
No. I didn't say that exactly.
No. I did.
Oh. I see.
You think if we get close again.
I might be ruthless with you.
Maybe.
But I know I might.
I'm someone who breaks things.
remember?
I think maybe
I always have been.
Except now I'm armed.
I think you're in
the wrong house. friend.
You might wanna leave
before you get hurt.
You're not Julian Carson?
Morgan Bote's
personal field operative?
Let's assume
I'm in the right house.
and let's assume whatever it is
that you wish
I didn't know about you.
I know.
The email that Morgan Bote sent.
-I didn't get an email.
-It's critical that I see it.
Even if it weren't
a national security issue.
which I'm pretty sure it is.
there are lives at stake here.
The lives of people
who are counting on me.
I didn't get any email.
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
Now. please leave my house.
How did I find you?
The Old Man took care of
the people
he needed to take care of.
He built a wall around you.
around your name. your life.
so that nothing you did for him
could blow back on you
or the people you care about.
So. how on earth did I find you?
That wall was built
out of his influence.
The moment he was gone.
the cracks appeared.
There'll be more.
I imagine you have plenty
of enemies out there.
They'll show.
and you won't be safe.
And neither will the new girl
that you're seeing right now.
I am fucking certain
you did not just threaten her.
-Because if you did--
-It's not gonna be me
you need to worry about.
I'm fucking certain you're
smart enough to know that.
I spent a long time
living behind
one of those walls.
So trust me when I tell you
when they fall.
and the things you thought were
safe behind them are exposed
to the world...
there's nothing worse.
Help me.
and I'll help make sure that
your wall holds for a long time.
Don't. and you're on your own.
I feel very exposed right now.
Is that normal?
I don't know
what "normal" means
in this context.
I mean. I understand
that not everyone in this
restaurant is looking at me.
but it feels like
everyone in this restaurant
is looking at me.
Yeah. that's normal.
She's gone from very late
to extremely late.
Eh. You wanna split?
Go catch a show?
Ah.
I see what you did there.
Hoisted on my own...
Petard.
You know. I knew that.
It just sounded weird
as I was gonna say it.
It's a bomb.
It's from Hamlet.
Is it?
I mean. it's a bomb.
but the line is from Hamlet.
Which part?
What part of what?
Well. the play.
What part's it from?
I don't know.
Somewhere in there.
The "revenge-y" part.
Yeah.
Yeah. once you're
in a revenge story.
there are no other parts.
Oh. you should read
that play again.
First chance I get.
Can I ask you a question?
Shoot.
Where's our money from?
Well. your half
you stole from me.
No. no.
I'm-- I'm serious.
How did you make all this money?
Yeah. you do
what I do long enough...
...you come
across information
a lot of people wish
you didn't have.
You know. I got lucky.
I found a couple of guys
who had some cash to invest.
Right time. right place.
Who is Lou Barlow?
Where did you hear that name?
Morgan was talking about
how he couldn't believe
the stuff that
you got away with.
He mentioned the money.
and he mentioned that name.
And it was the only moment
I spent with him
that I could tell
he was being untruthful with me.
Hmm.
A lot of money changed hands.
That. uh. can bring
out the worst in people.
Lou Barlow is
the worst in people.
Yeah. he's a person I wish
I'd never crossed paths with.
Can you tell me
what that means?
Uh. someday.
Oh. Jesus. Really?
-We're leaving.
-Are you blowing off
my question?
No. we're just wasting time
sitting here.
We need to keep our heads
in the game.
You don't think she's coming?
I don't.
-You don't sound surprised.
-I'm not.
Who are you calling?
Nina Kruger's office.
Nina Kruger. please.
Oh. She's
unavailable at the moment.
ay I take your name and numberM
and someone will return
your call?
Is this Anna?
It is.
May I ask who's calling?
Uh. Anna.
this is time sensitive.
I'd like to know
where I can reach her. please.
I'm sorry.
she's out of the office
attending to a personal matter
and won't be
checking messages. but--
She's definitely not coming.
We're gonna need to go find her.
Her assistant just said
she doesn't know where she is.
Well.
I'm gonna ask her another way.
That thing actually gonna work?
Mmm. Theoretically.
As long as it's kept close
enough to the target. yeah.
And we're sure
that's her place?
Well. pretty sure.
So you just figured this all out
before we even left the US?
Yeah.
You found Kruger's assistant.
You found her place.
You-You constructed
this whole plan
without me even noticing.
Yeah. it wasn't like there were
state secrets involved.
I actually felt like I was
starting to understand all this.
which seems a little silly
at this moment.
Why?
All these moving parts
that I didn't even know existed
until I noticed that they
had been moving for days.
I mean. you're sitting there
building a laser rifle.
I-I understand it's not
a laser rifle.
I just--
I'm pretty sure
you understand my point.
Mmm. You understand
the hard parts.
The rest is just bells
and whistles. long division.
Part smart people hire
people like me to do for 'em.
Or used to do for 'em.
at any rate.
Excuse me.
Uh. I think I might be
a little lost.
I'm looking for my friend.
Uh. can you help me?
Who are you looking for?
I really appreciate it.
It's been a long day.
Thought I'd be wandering
these halls all night.
The friend I'm looking for
is named Nina Kruger.
Anna. look at me.
This was a courtesy.
The next time.
whether it's me or someone else.
you aren't gonna see it coming.
Are you sure it's worth it?
The person you are calling
is not available.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
I'm sorry.
I know you said I'm--
I'm not to call.
but there's a man
looking for you.
He came to my home tonight.
Please tell me
what I should do.
Please tell me.
I think it worked.
Yeah?
Uh. you did good. There it is.
There's the location
of Kruger's phone.
How did you know that that woman
would make that phone call?
Lucky guess.
How did you know?
You look someone in the eye.
you show 'em that
you're capable of doing
what they're most afraid of.
almost everyone will do
what you want them to do.
But not me.
You looked at me that way once.
I had a different reaction.
I found out
what you feared the most.
and I used it
to hurt you right back.
I know.
'Cause I am a person
who breaks things.
You okay?
I wish it hadn't been so easy
to do what we just did.
I wish it had been
harder to do that.
Near the end with Abbey...
you know. when she couldn't tell
what was real from what wasn't.
she said things that...
were hard to hear.
Oh. because they were mad.
But. I don't know.
maybe because they were true.
I once broke this dish.
You know.
dropped it in the kitchen.
She glared at me so--
so angry. so dark.
She said. "A person who
can't help but break
everything they touch...
shouldn't be allowed
in the house.
They should be outside
with the animals."
What part of that
felt true to you?
The worst parts.
If you're sitting there
thinking awful things
that you don't wanna say
because you can't imagine
anyone else understanding
about what sort
of person you are...
Just want you to know
that someone else does.
I don't wanna have to live
outside with the animals.
Me either.
Keep an eye out.
Give me a minute.
Oh. wait. Wait. Zoe.
-What happened?
-She's been poisoned.
- What?
-Something airborne in the house.
I have to assume I'm hot.
So j-- just keep your distance.
What-What-What can we do?
The guy I found in there.
he's got an antidote.
but it's destroyed.
They're gonna be coming soon.
We don't have much time.
You came.
W-We got lucky.
They didn't find it.
The study.
The middle shelf.
Hello. Zoe.
his is. uh. all so unfamiliar.T
I wish I knew how to start.
I have some very troubling
information.
I'm trusting you
to enlist the help
of Mr. Bote to address it
and to persuade him
to provide me with protection
of which I believe
I am in most urgent need.
A man named Suleyman Pavlovich
has used his mercenary army
to seize control
f an important mineral deposito
n the Panjshir.i
In the process.
his men were ordered
to murder the Hamzad family.
This much I believe you know.
Now let me tell you
what hardly anybody knows.
The Meshbahar deposit is
very large.
but there are others
around the world.
Unfortunately.
most are located in places
that are not friendly
to my government or yours.
I have learned that a number
of those parties are engaged
in a secret plan
to organize themselves.
A cartel.
conceived to control access
to the world's markets
of rare earth metals.
If successful.
it would constitute a weapon
capable of bringing any
Western economy to its knees.
or all of them.
Pavlovich's membership
to this cartel promises
to be incredibly lucrative.
but it is hanging on
by a thread.
Threatened by you.
By the two of you.
Henry and Marcia Dixon possess
both a stake in his firm
and past ties to the CIA.
The cartel have begun to doubt
his trustworthiness
because of this.
He will do anything
to eliminate any trace
of the connection.
You and me.
Please...
help me.
So what do we do?
We separate.
-No.
-Yeah.
There's no choice.
We need to put you
someplace safe.
You're gonna go to the police.
We're gonna call Harold.
He can help.
-I thought we were past this.
-Zoe.
You running off
-and jumping off cliffs
to protect me...
-Zoe.
...as if that is
something that I wanted.
There's an antidote
to whatever I walked into.
but they've got it.
My only chance to avoid
what happened to her
is to let 'em take me.
I will make it back.
You get anywhere near Pavlovich.
you are not gonna be thinking
about anything
but killing Pavlovich.
I'll make it back.
I don't believe you.
I need you to.
Zoe...
I don't wanna do
this work anymore.
I don't wanna be in any more
of those situations.
That's why I left. I was clear.
Well. that's
between you and him.
I didn't ask to be here.
In a moment when I think
he believed
that his life's work
was about to be undone.
he put its survival
in your hands.
I don't care
about his life's work.
Hey. I don't either.
I'm here because
I want my life back.
and I don't know
any other way to do it.
Why are you here?
He sent an email
the other night.
I deleted it. and it felt good.
I was free from it all.
I closed my eyes
and tried to go back to sleep.
And then what did you do?
I undeleted it.
And why do you imagine
I would do something like that?
You're asking me?
I think you know what it's like
to be in my shoes.
I think you partnered with him
once and tried to leave.
So. yeah. I'm asking you.
May I?
So why couldn't you
just let it go?
Maybe it was because you knew
he was trusting you
with something important.
And it was very hard
to walk away
from something that was
a part of who you are.
I just said
I don't want it anymore.
Maybe want has nothing to do
with something like that.
And then maybe
you just don't like the idea
of someone taking a shot
at the Old Man
and getting away with it.
And you'd like to be the one
to do something about it.
When I opened it. I thought
maybe he sent it by mistake.
I mean. the man was really old.
This wasn't a mistake.
You know who that is?
This
is Suleyman Pavlovich.
And that is my ex-wife.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm